

Mars Bryant

4705 Bay Street Toronto United States **E-mail:** p2emetafox0311@gmail.com **Website:** https://coke.liderkof.com.br

Phone: +1 850 252 8258

OBJECTIVE

6+ years of experience and well versed in all phases of the Metaverse development life cycle, with a strong working knowledge of programming practices. Dedicated freelancer team member and leader with passion for game development.

I am currently seeking a dedicated job. :)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelancer.com

April 2018 — Present

Game Developer

• Unity Game Developer

February 2017 - PRESENT

Combination of React.js project and Unity game.

P2E game using Nethereum and Solana Web3.

Pioneered multiplayer games using Photon Engine and Colyseus.

a Metaverse game based on a virtual environment.

Games with Phaser, three.js and create.js

3D material texture Improvement skill without high load.

• C++ Game Developer

May 2016 - September 2017

Attended 3D MMORPG game development in C++.

Worked on a 3D game client, game engine and game servers using C++.

Profiled and optimized so many parts of the game client.

Developed a fast ozine terrain map generator.

Researched physics simulation synchronization through the network.

Polyphony Digital

September 2016 — April 2018

Game Developer

Worked as a Junior Game Developer.

This was my first company after graduation of my University.

Company URL: https://www.polyphony.co.jp/

id Software

May 2018 — March 2020

Game Developer

I collaborated with this company.

I took part in "Rage 2" game making.

My role in this game was Lead Developer of Character Motion part.

Company URL: https://www.idsoftware.com/

QUALIFICATIONS

• Certified Game Developer.(CGD)

EDUCATION

Computer Science

March 2011 — April 2016

NUS

Obtained Bachelor's Degree.

Mars Bryant

PORTFOLIO My past Work.

https://coke.liderkof.com.br https://crosmoshooter.com

https://d3fqtz6zjfopso.cloudfront.net https://pacverse.punkyapesclub.com/

INTERESTS Basketball, Volleyball, ESports, Guitar...

 $REFERENCES \qquad \qquad https://coke.liderkof.com.br$

Email: p2emetafox0311@gmail.com

Phone: +1 850 252 8258

SkypeID: @live:.cid.ab116d7e2b664771

Mars Bryant 2